<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>#randomdots (Posts related to blogsite)</title><link>https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/</link><description></description><atom:link href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/categories/cat_blogsite.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2023 &lt;a href="mailto:jeanbourgain8@gmail.com"&gt;Hasanth&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;a rel="license" href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/"&gt;
&lt;img alt="Creative Commons License BY-NC-SA"
style="border-width:0; margin-bottom:12px;"
src="https://i.creativecommons.org/l/by-nc-sa/4.0/88x31.png"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 11:11:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Tryst with ISI-Delhi</title><link>https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/</link><dc:creator>Hasanth</dc:creator><description>&lt;h5&gt;Table of Contents&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;div class="toc"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#1-background-information"&gt;1. Background Information&lt;/a&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#11-summary-2012-2019"&gt;1.1 Summary: 2012 - 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#12-summary-2019-present"&gt;1.2 Summary: 2019 - Present&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#2-introduction"&gt;2. Introduction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#3-theoretical-cs-to-theoretical-economics"&gt;3. Theoretical CS to Theoretical Economics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#4-need-some-more-time"&gt;4. Need some more Time!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#problems-solutions"&gt;Problems ? Solutions ?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#5-extras"&gt;5. Extras&lt;/a&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/#how-did-i-zero-in-on-isi-delhi"&gt;How did I zero in on ISI-Delhi ?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id="1-background-information"&gt;1. Background Information&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id="11-summary-2012-2019"&gt;1.1 Summary: 2012 - 2019&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary&gt;[Click To Expand]&lt;/summary&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/images/2012-2019.png" alt&gt;
&lt;em&gt;please open the image in a new tab for better clarity&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For an elaborate description of my works during 2012-2019, read - &lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/"&gt;Past, Present &amp;amp; Future - I&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="12-summary-2019-present"&gt;1.2 Summary: 2019 - Present&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary&gt;[Click to Expand]&lt;/summary&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/images/2019%20-%20Present.png" alt&gt;
&lt;em&gt;please open the image in a new tab for better clarity&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For an elaborate description of my works from 2019-Present, read - &lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/"&gt;Past, Present &amp;amp; Future - II&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="2-introduction"&gt;2. Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Sir&lt;/strong&gt;, to my fortune I have found a great &lt;strong&gt;possibility&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;strong&gt;Sept'2022&lt;/strong&gt;, which was the same month in which I gave my UPSC-CSE (Mains) Exam. The &lt;strong&gt;possibility&lt;/strong&gt; has profoundly excited me to an extent that I was even ready to deliberately flunk my exam (only to appear again in next year - 2023). Till then, I have half-heartedly accepted &amp;amp; planned to delay my research pursuit for 5-7 years to comply with the rules of govt. (min. time one should spend in service to obtain a study leave), but this discovery of a &lt;strong&gt;possibility&lt;/strong&gt; has &lt;strong&gt;rekindled&lt;/strong&gt; my spirit to pursue research without having to delay it any further. Prior to this, my actual plan was to appear in UPSC-CSE (for IAS/IFS), finish my M.A. Economics at IGNOU so that I can appear for Indian Economic Services as a backup option. Naturally, it might occur to you when I'm so interested in research &lt;strong&gt;"Why not I pursue it single-mindedly and become a Research Scientist/Professor ? "&lt;/strong&gt; with much many opportunities existing today to work on Electronic Commerce/Algos/Networks etc., especially in CS after the advent of machine learning boom, be it at Google/Microsoft/Amazon Research and many other MNCs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2019 (Jun), I have made a steadfast decision to work for the state (govt.) as an organisation in an administrative position be it either in Administrative/Foreign Services and pursue research as a &lt;strong&gt;habit&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;not as a hobby&lt;/strong&gt;; but with dedication). Also, the fact that I find it very hard &amp;amp; contrasting to my personality, to dedicate myself to one particular area/subject for an extended period of time (&amp;gt;10-15 yrs) has completely ruled out the option of even thinking to become a full-time professor. That's why, to work for the state in an administrative capacity &amp;amp; also to retain independence in my breadth of interests - Maths, Theoretical CS &amp;amp; Economics etc., I have chosen this particular path.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="3-theoretical-cs-to-theoretical-economics"&gt;3. Theoretical CS to Theoretical Economics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have observed that ISI-Delhi provides an opportunity though not recommended yet it is open to consider a possibility for one to pursue their PhD remotely (not as a full-time). In my enquiry, I have come to know that there are people who are pursuing/have pursued research part-time (Ex: Leena Kumar etc.). Now, this possibility has come as an absolute blessing to me. I do not have to wait/delay my plan of pursuing research further for 5-7 years anymore.   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After spending some time working on projects till Jun'2019 in resolving the dilemma of my future pursuit between Theory &amp;amp; Applied aspects of Machine Learning, I have realised that my inclincation was more towards Theory. Since then, I've been exploring (briefly) theory in different areas apart from Machine Learning within the computer science (Algorithmic Game Theory, Approximation Algos, Graph Theory &amp;amp; Combinatorics etc.) keeping myself updated about the directions of research works. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some professors whom I follow in Computer Science (Click to Expand)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Prahlad Harsha &amp;amp; Othrs. at TIFR, Siddharth Barman (Fair Division) at IISC &amp;amp; groups working at Google &amp;amp; Microsoft Research in India, U.Penn (Sampath Kannan), UW (Anna Karlin, Sebastian Beubeck, Yin-tat-Lee etc.), UCSD (UIUC (Jugal Garg, Ruta Mehta etc.), Princeton (Matt Weinberg etc.), Harvard (Madhusudhan etc.), CMU (Pradeep Ravikumar, Venkatesh Guruswami etc.) and many other groups at MIT (Constantis Daskalias etc.), Columbia (Tim Roughgarden etc.), UW-Madison (Nowak, Suchi Chawla moved to UT-Austin etc.), Stanford (Andrea Montanari, etc.) &amp;amp; people at many others places - UWaterloo, Toronto, Oxford, ETHZ, EPFL etc.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Recently, after re-aligning my interests with Economics as primary focus from Theoretical CS in Sept'22 (Theoretical Economics $\succcurlyeq$ Theoretical CS) , &lt;strong&gt;I have found ISI-Delhi with You &amp;amp; Prof. Arunava Sen as crown jewels to my this new world&lt;/strong&gt;. Adding to it, "&lt;ins&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the possibility of pursuing research remotely&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;" has only made the feeling even more concrete. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this regard, from Oct'22 I have started to pickup the basics of the subjects with the help of M.A. Economics course at IGNOU. I felt it was the best option to pursue, simultaneously that way I could also earn a degree. If in case, not even in my wildest dreams I would allow, but if anything goes wrong with the UPSC-CSE, I can appear for Indian Economic Services ( for which M.A. Economics is compulsory) as a backup option. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="4-need-some-more-time"&gt;4. Need some more Time!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though the ISI-JRF (QE) exam primarily focuses on foundational depth with some deducable patterns existing in the questions asked - Utility Maximization, Theory of Choice, Econometrics Basics + Dev Econ., Time Series Basics, Growth Models, Nash &amp;amp; Sub-Perfect Nash Equilibrium (one year they were missing). I came across some instances where the terminologies appearing in the exam which are not quite common at the first instance (Ex: $2^{nd}$ Question's Perfect Labour Mobility in QEB, 2018 etc.) for someone like me. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If not for both ISI-JRF &amp;amp; IGNOU exams, I would have strictly confined myself to Microeconomic Theory and tried to cover as much material as possible restricting exclusively to these topics at first - Theory of Choice, Equilibrium &amp;amp; Welfare, Game Theory, Mechanism Design &amp;amp; Auction Theory + Mathematical Programming (Graphs for Networks &amp;amp; Linear Programming) following your notes for the foundations build up. But I'm having a feeling that I will need some more extra time inorder to cover them more broadly &amp;amp; concretely, also to fill my gaps of knowledge in Econometrics (despite familiarity with Max. Likelihood, Regression etc.) &amp;amp; Macroeconomic Theory (appears quite broad to me), especially UPSC-CSE preparation constraing my time. I may have completed my 1st year M.A. Econ - IGNOU exams in Dec'22, but I did not find the material sufficient enough to cover the breadth &amp;amp; depth required for ISI-JRF. I found them more verbose.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clash of UPSC - CSE, ISI-JRF (QE), Indian Economic Services, 2nd year M.A. Economics - IGNOU Exams (Click to Expand)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
UPSC-CSE being primarily a memory-based exam and me aiming for a top-rank in the exam, is demanding a major portion of my day-time along with its Mathematics Syllabus (almost equivalent to M.Sc Level). If it is not for Mathematics &amp;amp; it's vast syllabus (but fetches more marks), I think UPSC-CSE would have been much easier to be done away with.
All of the exams happening around the same time, it has become quite difficult for me to optimally allocate my attention &amp;amp; memory in order to obtain the best results in all. To my luck/bad-luck my 2nd year M.A. Economics exams of IGNOU in Jun'23 are clashing with Indian Economic Services exam dates, preparation for these two has been demanding a lot of my head memory, both of them being verbose. So, for their sheer size in material and also clashing of dates I have decided not to appear for Indian Economic Services Exam this year &amp;amp; changed my plan to give my 2nd year M.A. Economics exams in Dec'2023. With this only UPSC-CSE &amp;amp; ISI-JRF (QE) exams remaining, yet both being in May'2023 with contrasting demands of the subjects where QEA of ISI-JRF (QE) requires Probability &amp;amp; Statistics, Optimization etc., UPSC-CSE (Maths) demands primary focus on ODEs, PDEs, Mathematical Physics, Group Theory, Real Analysis etc., with only Linear Algebra &amp;amp; Calculus being common to both.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
All in All, despite cutting down the number of exams to appear in, both UPSC-CSE &amp;amp; ISI-JRF being broadly demanding in subject breadth, it has become quite difficult for me to manage &amp;amp; work towards producing best results in both, especially without any guidance. To address this problem I have found a solution but I would like to check them with you and verify before I can proceed. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="problems-solutions"&gt;Problems ? Solutions ?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instead of appearing for the exam in May'23 and joining the campus in Aug'23, Can I instead seek admissoin starting from Sept'23 ?&lt;/strong&gt; If I'm ready to take any kind of examination which the admission board demands from me - written/interview etc.
 &lt;br&gt;
&lt;details&gt;
   &lt;summary&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Solution:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;
   By doing this I can provide maximum attention to UPSC-CSE untill I finsh off the exams in Sept'23. Also, this would provide me more than enough time for me to concretely establish my foundation strongly in Micro Theory - Choice &amp;amp; Welfare, Game Theory, Mechanism Design &amp;amp; Auctions, Network Theory I will also try to extend my knowledge after initially covering your notes at first  in these topics. Also, I shall fill my gaps in the knowledge of Econometrics &amp;amp; Macro Theory by that time much more beyond the requirements of the ISI-JRF Exam. Once, I get done away with UPSC-CSE properly by securing a top-rank, I will whole-heartedly be able to dedicate myself to research.
   &lt;/details&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is ISI-JRF (QE) exam the only way to join the PhD program with a fellowship ? Can I instead start my PhD program on your SERB grant for the period Sept'23 - Jul'24 and clear the exam in 2024 for JRF ?&lt;/strong&gt; So that, in future despite of getting into Civil Services, I will be eligible for grants to conferences, book-purchasing etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id="5-extras"&gt;5. Extras&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id="how-did-i-zero-in-on-isi-delhi"&gt;How did I zero in on ISI-Delhi ?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started my research pursuit with &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1baLe5P9N5wIfxbIhuJDW9uw_jOTpaQQU/view?usp=sharing"&gt;Bio-Medical Devices &amp;amp; Imaging&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1IwRRM0X6Xsn-6FphBChUmscy894OCHYl/view"&gt;Instrumentation&lt;/a&gt; and have walked a long path experimenting in different areas - &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1LS3Y6dzPuQ-YZN2ZHMHlZPWwNeGkSEyo/view?usp=sharing"&gt;Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://github.com/anhttran/3dmm_cnn"&gt;Applied&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1y33JUi8W0MT1X8cHpywhF-WbSSGmsKKO?usp=sharing"&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1hmHOy27Xk3FgPk-aof9BHi59bLE3XmL4/view"&gt;Theory&lt;/a&gt;), &lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/1612.00523v1.pdf"&gt;3D&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://flame.is.tue.mpg.de/"&gt;Face&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://smpl-x.is.tue.mpg.de/"&gt;Body&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://grail.cs.washington.edu/projects/AudioToObama/"&gt;Reconstruction&lt;/a&gt;, SLAM (typically called as &lt;a href="https://grail.cs.washington.edu/projects/personnerf/"&gt;NERFs&lt;/a&gt; recently) etc. where some happened to be co-incidental (includes job at HPE) with the trends and others well thought ones (exploring Theory). For this, I do believe that my graduation course is also partly responsible where unlike other core branches such as EE, ECE, CS etc., Instrumentation Engg. curriculum at IIT-KGP happens to be a mix of all three with little specific to Instrumentation, limited by its extent of applications. It was only in 2019 (mid) I have concretely realized that my interests primarily lie in the intersection of Maths, Theoretical CS &amp;amp; Economics subjects, and resolved to pursue research for the coming next 10-15 years in these fields. I was supposed to join in one of Masters CS programs starting from June'2019 but for some specific reasons, and also having realized by then already that I like Theory a lot more than the Applied aspects of research, I have dropped my masters plan abroad (avoiding to spend any sums) and chose the path of Civil Services with a plan to do a PhD down the line after 5-7 years being in the service (which is allowed complying with the rules). Till then, I actually planned to pursue research independently more as a habit and enter into a PhD program in future with problems identified well beforehand to work upon.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid>https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-03-10%3A15%3A45/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 04:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Past, Present &amp; Future - II</title><link>https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-01-16%3A30%3A39/</link><dc:creator>Hasanth</dc:creator><description>&lt;h5&gt;Table of Contents&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;div class="toc"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-01-16%3A30%3A39/#2019-present"&gt;2019 - Present&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-01-16%3A30%3A39/#summary"&gt;Summary:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-01-16%3A30%3A39/#references"&gt;References:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="2019-present"&gt;2019 - Present&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="summary"&gt;Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/images/2019%20-%20Present.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="references"&gt;References:&lt;/h2&gt;</description><category>self</category><guid>https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-03-01-16%3A30%3A39/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Past, Present &amp; Future - I</title><link>https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/</link><dc:creator>Hasanth</dc:creator><description>&lt;h5&gt;Table of Contents&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;div class="toc"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#2012-2016"&gt;2012 - 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#2016-2019"&gt;2016 - 2019&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#summary"&gt;Summary:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#references"&gt;References:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/images/luffy.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="2012-2016"&gt;2012 - 2016&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I graduated with a Bachelors Degree in Instrumentation Engineering (EE) from IIT Kharagpur in 2016. During my bachelors, I started with working on Biomedical Devices, Instrumentation in 2nd year (summer) planning to specalise in Bio-Medical Instrumentation. 
Later, in my third year I associated with PhDs working on Bio-Medical Imaging &amp;amp; Machine Learning (Applied) at School of Medical Sciences (SMST) - IIT KGP. In 3rd year summer (2015), I did an internship at Reliance Industries Ltd., Surat. There, in recognition to my work, I was specially &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1IwRRM0X6Xsn-6FphBChUmscy894OCHYl/view?usp=share_link"&gt;felicitated&lt;/a&gt; by VP-Engineering for solving a long-standing problem in their Rubber Manufacturing Plant. For this, I was also awarded a Pre-Placement Offer (I didn't take up the offer). 
In my final year, I got placed in Hewlett - Packard Enterprise - HPE (they said it was R&amp;amp;D while recruting, buggers ended up making me do software).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Variational Bayesian Matrix Factorization for Bounded Support Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:1"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, is the title of the &lt;a href="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/xpl/RecentIssue.jsp?punumber=34"&gt;IEEE-TPAMI&lt;/a&gt; paper which I took up for my graduation thesis project. I found errors in their core algorithm equations and informed about the &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1hmHOy27Xk3FgPk-aof9BHi59bLE3XmL4/view?usp=share_link"&gt;corrections&lt;/a&gt; to them, which they had accepted but sadly, the corrections weren't significant enough to write a fresh paper. 😕&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projects that I worked on during my Bachelors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modelling the Transitions in Lung cancer cells and classification of different cells using Deep Belief Networks.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modelling different stages of epigenomic cells and classifying them into 4 different transition stages with an accuracy of 97.5% and 89.9% respectively for binary and multi-class problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Measurement of Fiber Angular Orientation Distributions in the Lung Cancer Cells&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:2"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:2"&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using the fourier components for determining the orientation. Can be used to identify the alignment of objects with good accuracy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARMS-Robotic Arm Sleeves&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interfaced EMG sensors and IMU with a robotic arm using Xigbee protocol and Atmega 16 microcontroller for mimicing the human arm movements.(group project)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Worked on classification of Alzheimer’s diseased and non diseased persons with EEG&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using EEG signal features for classifying diseased and non diseased person.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Examination of various feature extraction and selection techniques for binary classification problem of Right half and Left half brain activity based on EEG signals.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:3"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:3"&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performing Pre processing using STFT transformation and using alpha,beta,etc. components as features to classify&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design and Construction of a low cost Digital PH-meter using constant phase element as sensor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:4"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:4"&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed and constructed a low cost PH-meter from scratch using Operational-Amplifiers and Logic gates(for condition-ing the output of sensing element, PMMA, DQN-70 coated probes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analog circuit design for Measuring Heart Rate and Blood flow rate - Plethysmography&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed and constructed circuitry for measuring the blood flow rate using plethysmography technique from basic low-pass filters and Instrumentation Amplifiers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sanjeevani&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conceptualized and designed a prototype of a product which is made by bringing all kinds of card tests in one compact machine to detect conditions of diseases (group project).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few courses I took during my bachelors which aligned with my then interests: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Machine Learning, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computational Methods &amp;amp; Algorithms in Signal Processing, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Probability &amp;amp; Statistics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Image Processing, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information Theory, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer Networks etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my bachelors, I have been part of various extra-academic activities. I was part of a Gold-Winning Ad-Design Team, Product Design Team, Chemical Innovation Team &amp;amp; Hardware Modelling Teams. I also played some hockey briefly during my 2nd year. 
I have also guided some of juniors for an Open-IIT Product Design Competition. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="2016-2019"&gt;2016 - 2019&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I joined HPE in &lt;strong&gt;Aug'16&lt;/strong&gt;, there I worked on Spring Boot Frameworks, Hibernate etc. Initially, I did some (junk) Splunk setup &amp;amp;  Automation works. Later, some UI bugs they made me fix and by the end I was mostly doing some Backend stuff (on whole, I got some full stack experience) for a Network Security Product. I didn't find the work much interesting, I realized that I would be better at doing R&amp;amp;D works than software. 
So, I resigned in &lt;strong&gt;Sept'17&lt;/strong&gt;, hoping to apply for Masters in 2018 (starting MS in 2019), after spending some time on my own to identify my interests precisely. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During this period, from graduation till my resignition &lt;strong&gt;(Aug'16 - Aug'17&lt;/strong&gt;), I have gained some interest in &lt;a href="https://www.irakemelmacher.com/"&gt;Prof. Ira Kemelmacher's&lt;/a&gt; working areas - 3D Facial Reconstruction, SLAM (partly) etc. Also, back then, there wasn't much buzz about Deep Learning etc. yet, not at least in India. Though Yann's, Hinton's &amp;amp; Fei-Fei's models were just starting to make some noise, they didn't get much attention (that's what I think). The pre-doc programs at MSR-India, Google etc., were also not so well known back then. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I resigned my job at HPE, but had to spend some time on the growing heap of works then (ML &amp;amp; DL buzz just got picked up) to decide upon my interests between ML Theory &amp;amp; ML Applied. 
For my thesis, I worked on Machine Learning Theory, but I also started gaining some interest in 3D Facial Reconstruction, SLAM etc. So, to check with the dilemma, I decided to apply for Research Assistanship at IISC - CSA. At that time, having some of prior experience a little statistically inclined, I found Ambedkar Dukkipati for (ML-Theory) &amp;amp; VAL Lab in CDS (for ML in images - Computer Vision etc.) as professors suitable to work with. I applied for VAL Lab and was asked to attend an interview for an RA Position. I did attend, but came back in the middle of the interview after having some argument with them about their notations on Regression's Cost Minimization Function and an equation related to the function which they asked me to derive. Also, I realised that they wanted me more for the implementation parts of the project than for the theoretical understanding of workings of Deep Learning on images. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I returned to home, used up the last amounts of my salary left in my bank account to &lt;a href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Substack/Product/Code/System%20Maintenance/deep-learning-setup/"&gt;build a PC&lt;/a&gt;. It costed me around 1 Lakh, I assembled the PC myself, where I bought the parts in all kinds of sales. By that time, AWS &amp;amp; Google Cloud - GPUs &amp;amp; TPUs services weren't much known, I think they didn't even get started. So, that's why I had to burn so much of my money. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, between &lt;strong&gt;Oct'17 - Jul'18&lt;/strong&gt;. I built my PC, installing all softwares &amp;amp; their patches, version matchings (all of this took loads of time, which one might easily misjudge as too much since it is has become very easy now to create a setup ready for ML &amp;amp; DL works). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;May'18&lt;/strong&gt;,  I've participated in two Ideathons (Ideas' Hackathons) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hackerearth.com/challenges/hackathon/rupay-contactless-ideathon/"&gt;Rupay Contactless Ideathon&lt;/a&gt; (by NPCI, related to UPI Payments)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hackerearth.com/challenges/hackathon/pg-global-innovation-challenge/"&gt;P&amp;amp;G's Global Innovation Challenge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Rupay's Hackathon, I was one (solo) of the &lt;strong&gt;Top 10 finalists&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:5"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:5"&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; among 1.2K teams (2 allowed per each team). 
In P&amp;amp;G's hackathon, two of my solutions were shortlisted in &lt;strong&gt;Top 50&lt;/strong&gt; ideas, this too similarly around 1.2K teams took part (4 allowed per each team). I resigned and didn't proceed further to the next levels of hackathon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, I started by first picking up &amp;amp; working on concepts of 3D Facial Reconstruction. 
List below, are some of research groups whose works I have tried to build upon my product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hao-li.com/Hao_Li/Hao_Li_-_publications.html"&gt;Hao Li&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qX8AIRsFmTA"&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:6"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:6"&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; , &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dERjpAaoNjk"&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:7"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:7"&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.irakemelmacher.com/research"&gt;Ira Kemelmacher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:8"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:8"&gt;8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.patrikhuber.ch/"&gt;Patrik Huber's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:9"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:9"&gt;9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; was the most easily accessible work of all at that time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://ps.is.mpg.de/"&gt;Max Planck Institute(MPI)'s&lt;/a&gt; models for face&lt;sup id="fnref:10"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:10"&gt;10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; &amp;amp; body&lt;sup id="fnref:11"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:11"&gt;11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; - Amazon purchased the venture with the name &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Body_Labs"&gt;Body Labs&lt;/a&gt; which was being developed by these researchers at MPI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.yisongyue.com/research.php"&gt;Yisong Yue's&lt;/a&gt; group integrated the component of voices/lip movement to faces - &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9zL7qejW9fE"&gt;Demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:12"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:12"&gt;12&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://alexlattas.com/"&gt;Imperical College London's Group - ICL's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:13"&gt;&lt;a class="footnote-ref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fn:13"&gt;13&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; work was the most promising way for 3D Realistic Face Avatars. That's why Facebook bought their work right away. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have tried to access and replicate these works in order to come up with a product that would take in something like a 2D frontal face input and convert it to 3D avatar. I've gone through entire code bases and debugged their works, even found some errors in ICL's works and made them aware, to which they didn't care much to respond 😅.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From &lt;strong&gt;Jul'18 - Aug'18&lt;/strong&gt;, I have prepared for GRE and gave the exams. I got 169/170 in Maths, but 151/170 in English (320 overall). I knew that english would be my pain point at that time for GRE. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting back to 3D faces, somewhere in and around &lt;strong&gt;Sept'18&lt;/strong&gt;, Apple came up with its Augmented Reality (AR) Tech. by adding a depth front camera to its IPhone. It was with this, all my 3D Face Reconstruction dream world came down crashing to an end. Till then, I was trying to build something which would take in a 2D image and spit out a 3D caricature, with an addition of some voice regarding developments as well (possibly). But, the avatars which Apple came up with were so cool that how much ever I may try to come with a system that's efficient in 2D frontal image to 3D face conversion, it can never be as cool as Apple's due to its depth camera addition to the mobiles. All of a sudden, the friendly 3D reconstruction tech became so affordable, especially for faces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;Nov'18&lt;/strong&gt;, I was already late by then, I started collecting recommendation letters from professors &amp;amp; some of my mentors from my resigned workplace. I had to go to IIT to get recommendation letters from my bachelors advisor. Amidst this mess, when I went to Delhi to visit some of my friends who were preparing for UPSC already by then for more than over a year, a family issue arised which required my utmost attention. Majority of my time between &lt;strong&gt;Nov'18 - Jan'19 (mid)&lt;/strong&gt; went away in roaming around hospitals. During this time, simultaneously I finished my applications for Masters Programs in Computer Science. I applied to 4 colleges and got accepts from &lt;strong&gt;University at Buffalo - SUNY&lt;/strong&gt;,  &lt;strong&gt;University of Texas - Dallas (with scholarship).&lt;/strong&gt; But, I wasn't quite satisfied mith my accepts. I knew that my language skills have improved a little but I failed to recognise that they weren't good enough to write a gramatically correct &amp;amp; an engaging SOP. I must have taken some assistance, Sigh! 😕&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;Feb'19&lt;/strong&gt;, things became normal at home and running around hospitals has come to an end. The time spent at hospitals changed my outlook towards life drastically. I witnessed hospitals charging unscrupulous rates and treating with sub-standard equipment, especially those people, whose expenses are paid from the govt. health insurance policies - poor, employees etc. All such issues have pushed me to give a shot at UPSC, before I leave for Masters in &lt;strong&gt;Aug'19&lt;/strong&gt;. 
So, in &lt;strong&gt;Feb'19&lt;/strong&gt; without any knowledge, by just looking at some blogposts (Anudeep's etc.), I decided to pursue UPSC, picked up a few books online, shifted myself to Hyderabad to a secluded place and started preparing. As I wasn't much happy with the accepts and also having realised that my interests were more inclined towards theory, I dropped my plan of pursuing Masters (MS)  abroad (saving myself from hefty expenses). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since then, I have been in the UPSC journey and simultaneously charting out my career towards  becoming an independent researcher by habit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="summary"&gt;Summary:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/images/2012-2019.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="references"&gt;References:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="footnote"&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:1"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/6891337"&gt;Variational Bayesian Matrix Factorization for Bounded Support Data&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:1" title="Jump back to footnote 1 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:2"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1DygIi_wyObiks1YDIriD_fau0JtSNlx6/view?usp=share_link"&gt;Measurement of Fibre Angular Orientation Distribution of Lung Cancer Cells&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:2" title="Jump back to footnote 2 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:3"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.eswa.2014.02.043"&gt;Exploring Dimentionality Reduction of EEG Features in Motor Imagery Task Classification&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:3" title="Jump back to footnote 3 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:4"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/269932877_A_Phase_Angle_Measurement_Based_Conductivity_Sensor_for_Low_Conductance_Solution"&gt;A Phase Angle Measurement Based Conductivity Sensor for Low Conductance Solution&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:4" title="Jump back to footnote 4 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:5"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1P2OfnFEnbNLp9ATY9FQcftIDIfaO7Oai/view?usp=share_link"&gt;Rupay Contactless Hackathon's Finalist Certificate&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:5" title="Jump back to footnote 5 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:6"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/1612.00523v1.pdf"&gt;Photorealistic Facial Texture Inference using Deep Neural Networks&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:6" title="Jump back to footnote 6 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:7"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hao-li.com/publications/papers/siggraphAsia2017ADFSIFRTR.pdf"&gt;Avatar Digitization from a Single Image for Real-Time Rendering&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:7" title="Jump back to footnote 7 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:8"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/url?q=https%3A%2F%2Fgrail.cs.washington.edu%2Fprojects%2FAudioToObama%2F&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;sntz=1&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw3wKphmADwZ_WeCvS9do85c"&gt;Synthesizing Obama: Learning Lip Sync from Audio&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:8" title="Jump back to footnote 8 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:9"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.4dface.io/"&gt;4D Face&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:9" title="Jump back to footnote 9 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:10"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://flame.is.tue.mpg.de/"&gt;MPI's FLAME&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:10" title="Jump back to footnote 10 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:11"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://smpl-x.is.tue.mpg.de/"&gt;MPI's SMPL&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:11" title="Jump back to footnote 11 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:12"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://authors.library.caltech.edu/80375/1/a93-taylor.pdf"&gt;A Deep Learning Approach for Generalized Speech Animation&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:12" title="Jump back to footnote 12 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="fn:13"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/junior-geometry/Geo-ML-Health/poster/Alexandros-Lattas-Poster.pdf"&gt;AvatarMe: Realistically Renderable 3D Facial Reconstruction "in the wild"&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a class="footnote-backref" href="https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/#fnref:13" title="Jump back to footnote 13 in the text"&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>self</category><guid>https://jeanbourgain8.github.io/posts/Blogsite/2023-02-23-17%3A38%3A35/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 12:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>